jackinthebox.com 2015-09-14

# Jack In The Box | Legal and Privacy Policy

##  Legal Information & Privacy Statement

By using the pages in this site, you agree to these terms and conditions. If you do not agree, you should not use this site, but you are still very welcome at all of our restaurant locations.

## RESTRICTIONS ON USE

Material from [www.jackinthebox.com](http://www.jackinthebox.com/) and any other World Wide Web site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by Jack in the Box Inc. may not be copied or distributed, or republished, uploaded, posted, or transmitted in any way, without the prior written consent of Jack in the Box Inc. Modification or use of the materials for any other purpose violates intellectual property rights. Except as described otherwise, all materials in the Jack in the Box Inc. sites are made available only to provide information. All materials are provided "AS IS" without any express or implied warranty of any kind. Jack in the Box Inc. controls these sites from its world headquarters in San Diego, California, and makes no representation that these materials are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you use this site from other locations, you are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws.

## SUBMISSIONS

All remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, data, names, addresses, phone information or other information communicated to Jack in the Box through the Jack in the Box site or through electronic mail (together, the "Submission") will forever be the property of Jack in the Box Inc. Jack in the Box Inc. will not treat any Submission as confidential or proprietary and will not be liable for the use of any ideas for its business (including without limitation, product or advertising ideas) and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in future Jack in the Box Inc. operations. Without limitation, Jack in the Box Inc. will have exclusive ownership of all present and future existing, and even non-existing, rights to the Submission of every kind and nature everywhere in the known universe. Jack in the Box Inc. will be entitled to use the Submission for any commercial or other purpose whatsoever, including at our company picnic and in Jack's home movies, without compensation to you or any other person sending the Submission. You acknowledge that you are responsible for whatever material you submit, so please think twice before pressing send, because you, not Jack in the Box Inc. have full responsibility for the message, including its legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality, and copyright.

## RESTRICTION OF LIABILITY

Jack in the Box Inc. will not be liable for any damage or injury caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, delay in operation of transmission, computer virus, or line failure, or any other events you can think of. Jack in the Box Inc. will not be liable for any damages or injury, including but not limited to, special or consequential damages that results from the use of, or the inability to use, the materials in this site. The above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you to the extent that applicable law may not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental or consequential damages. The company's total liability to you (for all losses, damages, and causes of action, or otherwise) will not be greater than the amount you paid to access this site (nothing, right?). Jack in the Box Inc. does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use of the material contained in this site in terms of its correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. The material in this site could include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, in fact, no matter how many times Patti, Brian and Vikki read through it, there are probably a number of misspellings or things we didn't mean to say, or probably should have said differently, so we will definitely be making changes and updates every time Jack has a better idea.

## LINKS TO OTHER MATERIALS

The Jack in the Box Inc. web site may link to sites not maintained or related to Jack in the Box Inc. The linked sites are not under the control of or affiliated with Jack in the Box Inc. Jack in the Box Inc. is not responsible for the content of any other sites or any link contained in a linked site. Jack in the Box Inc. does not endorse third-party sites, companies or products to which it links. If you decide to access any third-party site linked to this site, you do so entirely at your own risk, so you take care out there.

## COPYRIGHT NOTICE

The graphic images, buttons and text contained in the Jack in the Box Inc. site are the exclusive property of Jack in the Box Inc. and may not be copied, modified, uploaded, published, posted, distributed, or displayed or reproduced or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without the prior written permission of Jack in the Box Inc.

## TRADEMARK INFORMATION

The following is a non-exclusive list of trademarks owned by Jack in the Box Inc.: Breakfast Jack, Carnivores and Design, Clownhead Design (2D), Clownhead Design (Antenna Ball), Clownhead Design (Clothing), Extreme Sausage®, Jack®, JACK CA$H®, Jack Design (3D with arms folded), Jack in the Box®, Jack in the Box and Design (Canted), Jack in the Box and Design (Horizontal), Jack Jr.®, Jack's Back®, Jack's Gear®, Jack's Kid's Meal and Design, Jack's Spicy Chicken®, Speakerbox®, Breakfast Jack®, Jumbo Jack®, Late Night and Design, Sourdough Jack®, Bonus Jack® and We Don't Make it 'til You Order It®.

Other trademarks are the property of the respective trademark owners. Jack in the Box Inc. trademarks may not be used publicly without the prior written permission of Jack in the Box Inc.

## MISCELLANEOUS

These terms and conditions will be governed and interpreted pursuant to the laws of the State of California, United States of America, Planet Earth, notwithstanding any principles of conflict of law. The services of Jack in the Box Inc. are available in select regions of the United States. There may be some products and services described in this site that may not be available at all locations. In addition, some of the promotional items, premiums, and prices may only be available for a specified time in certain areas.

### Privacy Policy

Jack in the Box Inc. respects your right to privacy on the Internet.

No personal information is automatically collected from visitors to its sites. However, certain non-personal information of visitors is recorded by the standard internet service operations of Jack in the Box Inc. This information is primarily used to provide an enhanced online experience for the visitor. Information tracked includes the type of browser being used by the visitor (e.g., Internet Explorer, Chrome, Firefox, Safari) the type of operating system (e.g., Macintosh, Windows) in use by the visitor and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T.) The location of the visitor’s IP address is used to reflect the nearest Jack in the Box restaurant on the mobile and desktop websites.

## EMAIL SUBSCRIPTIONS, TEXT NOTIFICATIONS, CONTESTS AND SIMILAR

Email addresses, mobile phone numbers and other personally identifiable information such as first and last name, home or other physical address or telephone number for visitors to this site are known only when voluntarily submitted by the user, for example via registration for sweepstakes or contests, content submissions, suggestions or participation of visitors in any available online interactive activities.

  * Jack in the Box Inc. collects the following types of information from individuals who opt into Email and Text databases:
  * First name
  * Zip Code
  * Gender – optional
  * Birthdate - optional
  * Email address
  * Mobile phone number

Users may choose to submit online to Jack in the Box Inc. names, email addresses, mobile phone numbers, gender, birthdate and/or zip codes from individuals who request to receive more information from Jack in the Box Inc. about its menu items, special offers or similar matters. All subsequent email communications include a link to easily unsubscribe from the email database. Unsubscribes can easily be submitted via www.jackinthebox.com/connect/unsubscribe.

Users must explicitly consent to receiving messages on mobile phones in order to sign up for text mobile messages. Users may text HELP to 31278 for assistance or text STOP to 31278 to opt out of mobile messaging. Message and Data rates apply to mobile communications.

More on how we use above info, what we do with it.

Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this site is retained by Jack in the Box Inc. and is not sold, transferred or otherwise disclosed except to our agency partners and other affiliated third parties or where disclosure is required by law. This information may be used for any of the following purposes: (1) receive special offers, product information and updates from Jack in the Box; (2) to help Jack in the Box Inc. better understand and reach visitors' use of our site; (3) to fulfill prizes; (4) to respond to specific requests from our visitors, including prospective franchisees; (5) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, where necessary; (6) to provide any necessary notices to our visitors or their parent or guardians, where necessary (7) to protect the security or integrity of our sites when necessary.

**Jack in the Box Inc. notifies visitors of changes to this privacy policy by changing the effective date on the text hyperlink to this policy.**

Jack in the Box Inc.'s website may provide links to other third-party websites which are not under our control and are not covered by this policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) sites, as we said before, be careful out there.

## USE OF COOKIES

When you view our web sites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the sites to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

## A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY

Jack in the Box Inc. believes that parents and guardians should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufactures that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without your permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please consult the "Consumer Assistance" page of the Direct Marketing Association home page (www.the-dma.org). You should also know that it is the policy of Jack in the Box Inc. that visitors under 18 years of age should not submit or post any information on our Web site without parental consent. If we learn that we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 18, we will delete that data from our systems.

## FRANCHISE INQUIRY COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Jack in the Box Inc. collects the following types of information from individuals who provide such information indicating that they are interested in becoming Jack in the Box® franchisees:

  * First and last name
  * Home and business addresses
  * Email addresses
  * Telephone numbers
  * Social Security numbers
  * Liquid asset information
  * Net worth information
  * Partnership information
  * Business ownership information
  * Occupation

Unless otherwise disclosed during the collection, personally identifiable information that may be collected in connection with visitors to this site is retained by Jack in the Box Inc. and is not sold, transferred or otherwise disclosed outside the company, except where disclosure is required by law.

None of the communications made through this website should be construed as an offer to sell any franchise in, nor is any such communication directed to, the residents of any jurisdiction requiring registration of the franchise before it is offered or sold in the jurisdiction. No franchises will be sold to any resident of any such jurisdiction until the offer has been exempted from the requirements of, or duly registered in and declared effective by, such jurisdiction and the required Franchise Disclosure Document (if any) has been delivered to the prospective franchisee before the sale in compliance with applicable law.

You may be provided a printed copy of our Franchise Disclosure Document (“FDD”) later in the consideration process. You may prefer to receive the FDD in pdf format on a CD. The CD will also contain a version of Adobe Acrobat Reader for your computer system to access the pdf file. To discuss the availability of the FDD on CD, contact the Franchise Department at 9330 Balboa Avenue, San Diego, CA 92123, [franchising@jackinthebox.com](mailto:franchising@jackinthebox.com). Unless we are notified otherwise, a printed copy will be sent you.

The submission of a Franchise Inquiry does not obligate the visitor or Jack in the Box Inc. in any manner, nor does it imply that there is any legal or commercial relationship between the two entities. It is further understood that Jack in the Box Inc. has the sole right to approve or disapprove the Franchise Consideration Request for any reason it may determine, and in the event that Jack in the Box Inc. disapproves the Franchise Consideration Request, Jack in the Box Inc. shall have no liability or ongoing obligations to me.

## ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Your access to and use of this and other Jack in the Box Inc. sites is subject to the above privacy terms and conditions and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this and other Jack in the Box Inc. sites, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these terms and conditions.

**Jack in the Box Inc. may at any time revised these privacy terms and conditions.** You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then current privacy terms and conditions.

_Effective January 16, 2013_

©Jack in the Box Inc. 2013 All rights reserved, of course.

## Signup

###  Get Some Tasty Texts

OR

###  Bacon-Infused Email
